budlightcointoss.com 2016-05-15

# Bud Light Super Bowl Coin Toss

Thank you for visiting our website (the "Website"). We value and respect your privacy, and this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and protect any information you may provide to us. Our Terms of Use available here describe the terms and conditions governing your access to and use of the Website. Your use of the Website signifies your agreement to be bound by both the Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website or provide any information to us. Anheuser-Busch is committed to complying with the requirements of the Beer Institute Advertising and Marketing Code. For more information, click here.

Unauthorized Use

The Website is not directed to, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from, persons under the age of 21. If you are under 21 years of age and have entered this Website by providing a false date of birth, you must immediately leave this Website. Under no circumstances may you use this website or submit personal information to us if you are under 21 years of age.  We are committed to compliance with all applicable regulations, laws, and rules, including those issued by the Beer Institute, ICAP, and COPPA.

The Information We Collect

In order to use the Website to submit comments, interact with other users, post reviews, and upload recommendations, you will need to create an account and provide several types of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"). We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable, indirect and/or aggregate information as a result of your use of, and interaction with, the Website (collectively, "Usage Information").

Personal Information

When you create your account, we may ask you to provide Personal Information. Depending upon the activity you are attempting to complete, this may include any of the following:

  * name
  * e-mail address
  * date of birth
  * mailing address
  * mobile phone number
  * credit card information
  * other personal information as necessary

Also, your email address and/or your domain name may be automatically recognized when you visit our Website.

You may choose not to provide any Personal Information that we ask for. However, we only ask for as much Personal Information as is necessary to complete the activity you are requesting. As such, if you choose not to provide the Personal Information that we ask for, it is possible that you may not be able to participate in that activity or the full functions of the Website.

Opting-In and Opting-Out

You will usually be asked to agree to receive communications about special offers or programs from Anheuser-Busch Inc., and any of our affiliated brands or divisions at the time you provide your email address to us ("Opt-In"). In the event that you provide your email address via a channel that does not include a mechanism for you to affirmatively Opt-In, such as by email, you agree that by providing your email address, you are completing an Opt-In and that you will be responsible for opting-out of receiving any future communications about special offers or programs. You can do this by clicking on the link provided at the bottom of each email communication (each an "Opt-Out").

Usage Information

We may also use certain standard web measurement and tracking technologies such as "cookies," web server logs, or other statistics programs to collect Usage Information and track and record how you use the Website. If our Website offers shopping, we may use cookies to keep track of items in your shopping cart. This data is anonymous and does not personally identify you. Usage Information helps us measure the success of the Website and its features or pages and to improve your online experience. Your browser may have an option that allows you to accept cookies, reject cookies, or receive notification when a cookie is sent, but you should note that the use of such restrictive browser settings may limit your use of the Website. In addition, we may utilize use web beacons (also known as "action tags" or "one pixel .gif files") to recognize you when you visit the Website. We do not use spy ware, adware or any other similarly intrusive software. We may also use other technology, called clear GIFs, to provide us with other important anonymous information, such as when an e-mail has been opened.

Third Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies and/or media partners to serve ads on our Website and/or on the sites on which we advertise. Please note that these companies may use Usage Information about your visit to the applicable site in accordance with the policies on the site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. In addition, we may use web beacons provided by third-party advertising companies to help manage our online advertising. These web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this Website to learn which advertisements bring users to our Website. To learn more about third-party advertising companies, cookies and how to "opt-out" of this type of advertising, please go to[ ](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp&sa=D&usg=AFQjCNGNHfV5CAD_I6P2RXGtVQ3_BWRVpA)<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Credit Card Information

If you are making a purchase on the Website, you may be asked to provide credit card information. In such event, it is our policy to redirect you to a payment processing portal hosted by a third party payment processor. We do not collect, access, store or process any credit card information.  Please read the privacy policy on our payment processor’s website regarding the use, storage and protection of your credit card information before submitting any credit card information.

Use of Information Collected

We use your information for only the following business purposes:

  * to provide the services you request;
  * to respond to inquiries we receive from you or in connection with a transaction you initiate;
  * to analyze, manage and improve the Website;
  * to use it within Anheuser-Busch as we continue to work on being the world’s best beer company;
  * to notify you of special offers and other services that we believe may be of interest to you or to send you current mailings;
  * to provide you with advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you;
  * to notify you that you have been selected as a winner of a contest or sweepstakes;
  * to help us diagnose problems with our server or other technical issues relating to the performance of the Website; or
  * for any other specific business purpose stated at the time you provide your information.

We collect only the Personal Information necessary to complete the specific transaction that you request. We do not condition your participation in any specific activity on our Website on the disclosure of more Personal Information than is reasonably necessary to complete that activity. You expressly authorize us to share your personal information with certain third parties retained by Anheuser-Busch (who shall be subject to confidentiality obligations at least as restrictive as those imposed upon Anheuser-Busch by this Privacy Policy) to the extent necessary to perform any of the business purposes listed above. Please also note that in connection with certain requests, you may be transferred to different web site, which has a different privacy policy. Please review this privacy policy before using that website. If you do not want to be contacted for these purposes or if you would like to obtain a copy of the personal information gathered by this Web site or correct or delete such information from our database, please send us an e-mail with your concern or question by clicking[ ](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://contactus.anheuser-busch.com/contactus/public/age-gate_Budlight.aspx?websitecode%3DNONE&sa=D&usg=AFQjCNHClUNVK3TWTMnQPQeUIk5ZlzTY_w)[here](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://contactus.anheuser-busch.com/contactus/public/age-gate_Budlight.aspx?websitecode%3DNONE&sa=D&usg=AFQjCNHClUNVK3TWTMnQPQeUIk5ZlzTY_w). If you voluntarily disclose Personal  Information (e.g., name, email address, personal photographs) in a community forum, such information may be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. We have no control over this type use of your Personal Information and are not  responsible for that use.

Mobile Applications

From time to time, we may offer certain mobile applications, including iOS applications ("Apps"), for download. We will use commercially reasonable efforts, given the limitations imposed upon us by third party providers such as Apple Inc. and Google Inc., to clearly disclose what, if any Personal Information or Usage Information is collected by the particular App, how it is used, and with whom it is shared. Please note, certain practices are outside of our control, for example, tracking by Google, Inc., Apple, Inc., or your third party telecommunications carrier.  WE are not responsible for the actions of such third parties.  You should always read and understand the policies of any third party provider, such as Google with respect to Android apps and Apple with respect to IOS apps, and your wireless carrier, before making any purchase or downloading any app.

Text Messaging

From time to time, we may run certain campaigns that provide you with the ability to send a text message and Opt-In to receive future text messages. Your Opt-In request provides us with your mobile phone number. If you choose to Opt-In, you agree that we may, from time to time, send messages to the mobile device associated with that number about new products, promotions, services or offers. Although there is no fee associated with this service, your carrier may charge you for each message you receive in accordance with your calling plan. You agree that we are not responsible in any way for such charges. If you do not wish to continue to receive any messages via your mobile device, you may Opt-Out at any time by following the instructions provided in the text message.  Failure to Opt-Out after you have previously provided an Opt-In constitutes your consent to continue to receive these messages until you elect to Opt-Out, and your release of us from any carrier charges associated with such messages.

Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose the information we collect from and about you:

  * when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to:

  * identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of the Website, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities:
  * enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, investigate and defend against any third-party claims or allegations, and/or protect the security or integrity of the Website; or,
  * respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws;

  * to our business partners for research, analytical and marketing purposes, and/or to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing any request on your behalf, provided, that such business partners are bound by obligations of confidentiality with respect to your information that are at least as restrictive as those imposed upon Anheuser-Busch by this privacy policy; or
  * otherwise with your consent.

We may sell or buy other businesses or entities. In such event, we may transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In such transactions, your Personal Information may be included in the transferred business assets.

Also, in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used and your Personal Information may be included in the transferred assets.

We may use your Usage Information to identify and develop products and services that may be of interest to you and/or share this information with certain third parties for direct marketing purposes with respect to special offers, products, services, programs, promotions, surveys, publications, invitations or other opportunities that may be of interest to certain demographic groups.

We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future.

Under the laws of some jurisdictions, you may be entitled to request disclosure regarding how we share your Usage Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes ("Information-Sharing Disclosure"). To the extent required by applicable law, we shall provide the Information-Sharing Disclosure to you upon your written  request to Anheuser-Busch, Inc., One Busch Place, St. Louis, MO 63118.

Except as explained above, we will not share any of your personal information with any third party, unless we have received your express permission to do so.

Linked Sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites, including social media sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through third-party websites and expressly disclaim any liability related to such collection, use or disclosure. We are not responsible for any information or content contained on such sites. Links to other websites are provided solely as a convenience. Your browsing, use and interaction on any other websites, including websites which have a link to the Website, are subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please review the privacy policy posted on any website that you may access through, or which links to the Website.

Please note that if you provide information to us via a social media site or participate in a social media site linked to the Website, you consent to our use of your information for any reason as if it were submitted to us directly via the Website.

Security Procedures

We take commercially reasonable precautions and have implemented commercially reasonable technical measures to protect against the risks of unauthorized access to, erroneous disclosure of, and unlawful interception of Personal Information submitted via the Website or otherwise collected or possessed by Anheuser-Busch. However, your email transmissions and/or other communications containing Personal Information may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and/or the Website may be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative errors. We do not guarantee the security of any information transmitted over the Internet. Once we receive your Personal Information, we take commercially reasonable steps to limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees and service providers whom we determine need access to the Personal Information to provide the requested products, services, offers or opportunities that may be of interest to you. However, even after we receive your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed as a result of a breach of our commercially reasonable efforts or as a result of any other event beyond our reasonable control. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee that your Personal Information is completely secure and safe from such risks. For the avoidance of doubt, WE expressly disclaim any representation or warranty, whether express or implied, with respect to ensuring, guaranteeing or otherwise offering any definitive promise of security in connection with your PERSONAL Information or Usage Information.

Special Note to International Users

The Website is hosted in the United States. If you are attempting to access the Website from a physical location within the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that your use of the Website is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and the Terms of Use.  To the extent you provide Personal Information through the Website, you are transferring your Personal Information to the United States and you consent to:

  * such transfer,

  * the application of the laws of the United States and/or the State of Missouri with respect to any dispute arising from or related to the Privacy Policy and/or your use of the Website, other than such rules, regulations, case law, and/or international treaties that would result in the application of the laws of a jurisdiction other than the United States or the State of Missouri, and

  * the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the State of Missouri and the federal courts sitting in St. Louis, Missouri.

Any claim or dispute between you and us that arises from your use of the Website or in connection with the Privacy Policy shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in St. Louis, Missouri, U.S.A. You agree that such court shall have personal jurisdiction over you, you agree to submit to the jurisdiction and venue of such courts, and you waive any objection based on inconvenient forum.

Changes and Updates to the Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may revise the Privacy Policy. To help you stay current of any changes, we take the following two steps: (i) we note the date the Privacy Policy was last updated above; (ii) when we make a change to the Privacy Policy, we post conspicuous announcement of such changes on the homepage of the Website on the Website next to the link to this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Website following the posting of any revised Privacy Policy shall be deemed acceptance of the revised policy, so we strongly recommend that you review the Privacy Policy periodically. If, and only if, we make revisions to the Privacy Policy that result in a material lessening of the restrictions on our use or disclosure of your Personal Information, we will make a commercially reasonable attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such Personal Information. If you disagree with the terms of our Privacy Policy at any time, your sole remedy is to terminate your use of the Website and inform us of such termination as described in this Privacy Policy. Continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to the Privacy Policy  in effect.

Miscellaneous

If any part of the Privacy Policy is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of the Privacy Policy shall continue in force and effect.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please call us at 1-800-DIAL-BUD (342-5283) Monday through Friday, 11am to 8pm CST, or email us at crg@anheuser-busch.com.

Thank you for visiting our site.

Copyright 2014: Anheuser-Busch, One Busch Place, St. Louis, MO 63118
